Finding Aid for the A. Conger Goodyear Papers, 1683-1964 (bulk 1885-1964)
Buffalo History Museum. Research Library
- Albums and Scrapbooks, 1883-1963, XII.
  - Scrapbook, 1961 (Box 24, Volume 19)
Goodyear, Frank H. (Frank Henry), 1849-1907; Milburn, George (John George), 1880-1932; Cleveland, Grover, 1837-1908; Conger, A.G. (Anson Griffith), 1812-1880; Goodyear, Charles W. (Charles Waterhouse), 1846-1911; Goodyear family; Cornell, Katharine, 1893-1974; Wood, Leonard, 1860-1927; Museum of Modern Art (New York, N.Y.); Albright Art Gallery (Buffalo, N.Y.); World War, 1914-1918; World War, 1939-1945; Art--Collectors and collecting--New York (State); New York (State). National Guard. Regiment, 17th; New York (State). National Guard. Regiment, 71st
Genre Terms
Reminiscences; Photographs; Scrapbooks